Sean Remenyi 1/3/2020

My name is Sean Remenyi, I'm 29 years old and looking for a chef position to further my skills. I am from Canada and have over 10 years experience. I'm a hardworking, trustworthy and respectful worker, I have often ended up in management positions because of this and just enjoy creating dishes and helping with specials. I have all my Australian certifications (Cert III, IV and Diploma of hospitality), speak English fluently and have my Permanent Residency.

## Qualifications

Organized	Computer Skills (i.e. Microsoft Office)	Bilingual, English and French
Over 10 years of Experience in Kitchens	Hiring/Training of new Staff	Making and Checking Orders
Communication Skills	Can Work Independently or in Groups	Clean worker

### **Employment History**

## Red Spice Road, Australia September 2017-December 2019

Chef de Partie Asian Cuisine

- Run service and in charge of the kitchen on certain days.
- In charge of the larder section of the restaurant for over a year overseeing salads, apps, desserts and small plates.
- Teach and instruct to the other chefs of the section how to cook the dishes on the menu
- Help with the organization and the cleanliness of the kitchen
- Both opening and closing responsibilities for the kitchen
- General Kitchen Duties
- Completing services of over 400 covers

# Restaurant Foxy / Grumman '78, Canada May 2016-January 2017

Garde-Manger Seasonal/Mexican/Asian Cuisine

- Create Plates and weekly specials.
- In charge of the cold station which includes tartars, tataki, salads and ceviches.
- Regular kitchen duties and line cooking as well as prepping/executing/break down for banquets.

## L'Gros Luxe Sud-Ouest, Canada July 2015-February 2016

Sous-Chef Bar Cuisine

- Create dishes for the menu and weekly specials.
- Helped Organize the kitchen with storage of ingredients and deep cleans.
- Ran the Line for service, expedite orders, medium between front and back of house staff.
- General Problem Solving.
- Line cooking in every station and Night Manager for service.

# Cartel Street Food, Canada August 2013-May 2015

**Head Chef** 

Peruvian/Latin American/Asian Cuisine

- Create dishes for the menu and weekly specials.
  - Organized the kitchen in terms or Inventory lists and Storage of ingredients.
  - Weekly inventory, menu costing and placing orders for the restaurant.
- Find new suppliers, negotiate prices and follow-up if orders received didn't match.
- Maintained food and labor costs to an agreed upon standard.
- Maintaining the cleanliness of my kitchen.
- Hiring, firing and training of staff Opening/Closing the restaurant.

## Boneheads BBQ, Canada March 2013-June 2013

Morning Manager American BBQ Cuisine

• Responsible for opening the kitchen and the training of new employees.

E-mail: sean.remenyi@gmail.com

**Phone:** 0420652451

Sean Remenyi 1/3/2020

- In charge of placing orders for the restaurant.
- Regular kitchen duties and line cooking.

## McKibbins Canada March 2012 –August 2012

Night Manager Irish Pub Cuisine

- Responsible for the kitchen at night and on the weekends (their busiest shifts).
- Trained the new cooks, aided with the scheduling and responsible for receiving orders.
- Regular kitchen duties.

Hotel Ruby Foos/Typhoon Lounge/NextDoor Pub and Grill/La Sala Rosa, Canada Line Cook May 2009-March 2012 / August 2012-January 2013 Continental/Spanish Cuisine

- Prepare ingredients, plate dishes including sandwiches, salads, pizzas, burgers, tapas and paellas.
- Prepared and plated dishes for banquets of 100 people or more.
- Worked as part of a team as well as closing the kitchen nightly by myself.

#### Certification

Cert III in Commercial Cookery Cert IV in Commercial Cookery Diploma of Hospitality Management Food Safety Supervisor

#### **Alternative Experience**

Vancouver 2010 Olympics Dawson College, Westmount Mcgill University, Montreal Greet athletes, officials and ambassadors and help check accreditations

Graduated with honors in the Health Science Program.

Completed 2 years of General Biology and 1 year of Biochemistry.

**E-mail:** sean.remenyi@gmail.com

**Phone:** 0420652451